zunal.com 2017-12-15

# Welcome to Zunal.Com

Since 2001, we’ve listened to teachers, students, and parents to bring you the best service possible online — for free. Launched in May 2001, ZUNAL provides a free service for Preservice and Inservice teachers, and faculty to create WebQuests and share information online with others. By encouraging collaboration among our users, we provide a safe environment for students to learn, and teachers/faculty to educate. Since our launch, we’ve been in a process of continuous improvement and have relied on feedback from our users to refine our website.  
We hope to see you around on ZUNAL often! —  
ZUNAL ADMINISTRATOR  

Questions About WebQuests:  
If you are new to the WebQuest concept, please read our About WebQuest section.  
Questions About Zunal:  
If you have any technical problems and looking for technical support for ZUNAL you should first check out our FORUM pages. Please read to see if your question is already covered before posting your message. http://zunal.com/xforums.php  
Comments, Feedback, Suggestions about Zunal:  
If you have any comments, feedback or suggestions about the ZUNAL project please see forum http://zunal.com/xforums.php  

Our privacy policy is simple: we will never share any of your information — with anyone — for any reason.   
What personal information does ZUNAL collect?  
ZUNAL fully respects your privacy. During registration, the only personal information ZUNAL requires is: your display name and e-mail address. You may volunteer additional information once you are logged in to your personal account. Any personal information you provide to us WILL NOT be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of ZUNAL under any circumstance.   
External Sites   
ZUNAL is not responsible for the content on external websites (any URL not beginning with http://www.zunal.com). You are advised to read the privacy policy of external websites before disclosing any personal information to them.   
Questions?   
For inquiries or concerns, reach ZUNAL from the Contact page.   
Last Updated:   
May 15, 2001
